# PAIGE BOYD PRODUCT DESIGNER (UX/UI)

www.paigeboyd.co.uk

#### **PROFILE**

I am a self motivated, enthusiastic and ambitious Product Designer.

I design intuitive digital products with a focus on creating a meaningful user experience. I enjoy getting involved in every stage of the Product Design process, and always strive to learn new skills to better myself as a designer.



## **EXPERIENCE**

Associate - UX/UI Designer Synechron Dec 2020 - Present

Primarily working with Citi, I help them create the future of Product Control applications. I facilitate key stakeholder meetings, facilitate discovery and research workshops with users and BAs and work across the entire UX/UI process from ideation and user research to wireframing and prototyping.

**UX/UI** Designer June 2019 - Dec 2020

**Relative Ltd** 

I designed software for companies globally, ranging from simple mobile and web apps, to large, scalable systems. I worked across the full UI/UX design process, as well as designing company promotional materials and websites.

**Product Designer** Aug 2018 - Dec 2019 Paige Boyd Designs Ltd

Worked with clients across multiple industries to design websites, apps and platforms that align business needs with needs of customers. I also facilitated ideation workshops to create proof-ofconcepts for clients.

Clients included:

Danske Bank, Finmondo, Funds-Axis, TapSOS, Assistant.ly, Relative, CheckaTrade.

~~

**Content Designer Intern** Sept 2016 - July 2017

**Ulster University** 

#### **EDUCATION**

**BDes (Hons) Interaction Design** Ulster University, Belfast School of Art September 2014 - July 2018

**Award:** First Class Honours and Diploma in Professional Practice with Commendation. Deans List in Years 1,2 & 4.

Modules: Interaction Design, Designing with Content, UX & UI, Narrative & Storytelling, Dissertation Writing, Major Project Prototyping.



### ACHIEVEMENTS

**UI Design for Successful Software** July 2020

Certificate awarded by the Interaction Design Foundation (IDF) after successfully passing the course and assignments

**Deloitte Digital Experience Award** June 2018

The Deloitte Digital Experience Award recognises outstanding skill and creative thinking in Interaction Design. Awarded for: Signar (degree major project).

**EDGE Award (Ulster University)** June 2018



## MY TOOLKIT

**Figma InVision** Pen & Paper Adobe XD **Adobe Illustrator** Miro

Sketch **Basic HTML & CSS** 



#### CONTACT

design@paigeboyd.co.uk 07598801481 @ppppaige\_

References available on request.

